I've been wondering if it's really okay for the Dollars to exist.
ダラーズなんて 本当にあっていいのかなって思って…
I have to...
なんとか… なんとかしなきゃ！
I have to do something.
No matter what you learn about your partner or see her do, don't turn a blind eye to it.
相手の何を知っても 何を見ても 目を背けるな
A regular "gathering of the triumvirate."
まさに三頭両緒って感じだね
She wore a Raira uniform...
来良の制服を着て 胸が大きかったような…
a-and had big breasts...
I can't believe it.
ありえねぇ… ありえねぇよ あいつは…
I can't believe he'd...
The Yellow Scarves have surrounded some girl.
Where?
Behind the ward office... Oh, they're heading out. It looks like they're taking her somewhere.
What does she looks like?
That uniform...Maybe it's a Raira one? She's wearing a Raira uniform and has glasses...
And she has big breasts.
Why is Sonohara...?
どうして 園原さんが…
Everyone in the Dollars! This is an emergency!
That's right, we should all help each other!
We can't just let them keep doing whatever they want!
The Yellow Scarves have gone too far!
Well now...
さてと…
I'll enjoy the rest from the comfort of my living room.
続きはお茶の間でのお楽しみとしますか
Anyone who's close by, please help out! Everyone come together!
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Are you in the Dollars?
お前 ダラーズか？
You're the one who made a scene with the black biker, aren't you?
黒バイクと一緒にお騒がせしてくれたのもお前だろ？
Huh?!
You bitch.
この野郎
These people...are the Yellow Scarves?
この人たちは黄巾賊？
Oh, officer, over here!
お巡りさ～ん コッチです！ 早く 早く！
Hurry, hurry!
Tsk.
Wait!
待ちやがれ！ 待て！
Hey!
What did I do...?
私のしたことはなんだったのだろう？
This way.
コッチ！
Go straight. There's a door in the back.
まっすぐ行って！ 裏口がアルヨ！
I desperately thought I needed to do something.
何かしなければと 必死だった
Where the hell did she go?!
どこ行きやがった!
I found the girl. I got her to escape out the back of the Orb Ikebukuro building. They're still after her.
Is anyone near the Orb Ikebukuro building?!
But I've been confused and have done nothing but run away.
でも 私は混乱して 逃げて走ってるばかりだ
Panic! The exit's right there!
慌てて！ スグ出口ヨ～
The danger is cheaper than the fear!
案ずるヨリ安いおまんじゅうネ～
Why...?
どうして？
Alright, it goes "click."
はい ポチっとな
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
No fair, Horada!
法螺田さん！ ずるいっすよ！
The gourds, gaurds, guards for the Orb Ikubukuro building are also in the Dollars. Under and out!
Um, the area behind the Orb Ikebukuro building is where I work!
Who are you?
誰？
Why...?
どうして… どうして 助けてくれるの？
Why are you helping me?
Damn...
Are you all right, sir?!
大丈夫ですか! お客様
I helped out a bit; just one of the Dollars passing by. Well, I really was thinking about quitting, but...
Don't quit!
You can't quit!
I figured you'd come back.
A dream?
夢？
Where'd the girl go?
Is this...a dream?
これは夢ですか？
Move it!
どけ！
The girl has transformed into a bunny!
Dammit, where'd she go?
どこ行った？ ちきしょう！
You bastard...
てめぇ！
Won't you lose her if you don't hurry up?
早く行かないと 見失っちゃうんじゃないの？
Dammit!
くそっ！
What are you doing, you idiots?!
バカ！ 何やってる!
Wh-What happened?
ど… どうなってんっすか？
The Dollars are screwing with us.
ダラーズの連中が邪魔してるんだ 応援頼め
Call for backup!
We're going with numbers on this one!
こっちも数でいくぞ！ 数で
I'm being helped by people I've never met.
見知らぬ人たちが私を助けてくれる
It's like I'm having a dream.
それが夢を見ているみたいで…
The bunny's safely crossed the overpass!
うさぎちゃん 無事に渡ったっす
Togusa, pick her up.
渡草 車 出せ！
Roger that!
了解！
Fighting isn't good.
ケンカ よくないネ～ スシネタにするヨ！
I'll turn you into sushi.
They're ringing! There're so many of them!
鳴ってる！ すごい数！
Ours aren't the only phones that're going off, though...
鳴ってるのは味方だけじゃない あっちも…
Theirs are, too.
What? A girl in a bunny suit?
なんっすか？ うさぎの着ぐるみ？
A bunny suit?
With big tits?
Yeah. A bunny? Okay.
ああ うさぎっすね
Where did the bunny go? Whoever sees it, report it immediately!
Is that her?
あれか？
You can't tell if she's got big tits with that on, though.
あれじゃあ 胸が大きいか分っかんないじゃん
She'll just have to show them to us.
脱がせてみるしかねぇな
But...
でも
...my dream...
私の夢はいつでも私のうそだった
...has always been a lie.
Wait!
待て！
I'd only been having dreams about a happy family smiling cheerfully.
明るく笑う 幸せな家族の夢だけを見ていた
That's why this isn't a dream.
だから これは夢なんかじゃない 現実
It's reality.
That's what this hand taught me.
その手がそう教えてくれていた
And then, I suddenly realized...
それから 不意に気がついた
...that he knew about my hand.
この手を知っていると… 触れたことなどなかったのに…
Even though he'd never touched it before...
This is...
これは…
Um...
あの… あの！
How come you never notice what's important until it's too late?
大事なことは なぜ気づいたときにはもう失っているんだろう？
Kida...
紀田君… どうして？
Why...?
"Why," you ask?
どうして… か
Do you think it's weird I saved you from that group of Yellow Scarves?
黄巾賊に絡まれてるとこをオレが助けるなんて おかしいってこと？
Eh?
That's my erotically cute Anri for you.
さっすがオレのエロかわいい杏里ちゃんだ
That looks really good on you.
そんな格好も似合ってるね
Hey, can I ask you something?
ねえ 一つ聞いてもいい？
What are you doing?
杏里ちゃんは何をしているのかな？
What were you spying on us for?
こそこそ隠れて 何を探ってたわけ？
Tell me, Anri.
教えてよ 杏里ちゃん 何が目的？
What are you after?
I...You...
私は 紀田君が…
What about me? Is this my fault?
オレが何？ オレが悪いの？
Am I an idiot for protecting you?
杏里を守ろうとしたオレがバカ？
I guess I am.
だよね？
Don't...say that.
そんなこと言わないで…
Does Mikado know?
帝人はなんにも知らないの？
What were you planning to do about him?
あいつをどうするつもりだったの？
I...
私は…
Do you...
あいつの…
Do you think you understand him...
あいつの気持ちを分かってて…
Why won't you tell—
紀田君はどうして竜ヶ峰君に言えない…
Was it fun?! Tricking me and sucking up to him—
楽しかった!
オレをだましたり あいつに取り入ってさ！
What am I...saying...?!
何言ってんだ？ オレ…
I...
I just didn't want to hurt anyone or have you get hurt.
私はただあなたが傷ついたり 誰かを傷つけたりしてほしくなかっただけなのに…
I've run away from you, too.
あなたからも逃げ出してしまった 私は…
I...
There she is!
いた！
We found you.
見つけたぜ
You're in the Dollars, aren't you, bitch?
てめぇ やっぱりダラーズだな？
No, I'm not.
いいえ
Pft. Don't screw with us.
へっ ふざけやがって
Don't hide it now.
何を今さら
If you're not part of the Dollars, then what are you?!
ダラーズじゃないなら 何なんだよ？ お前は
You want to know...what I am?
私が何者なのか 知りたいんですか？
Hm? What?
ああ～？ なんだ？ 何なんだ？
What are you?
I said, "What are you?"
何なのだっつうんだ!
Oh, that's it! You're a crusader for justice!
ああ～ あれか
お前 正義の味方か？
You try to tempt us by saying, "Let's protect the peace!"
お前が 平和を守りましょうって 唆して
Well, we want to show you what happens when someone betrays us.
オレらを裏切ろうとしたヤツらがどうなったか 見せてやりたかったぜ
We beat the shit out of them!
とことん ぶちのめしてやったぜ
What...did I do...?
私が したことは…
And so, you can't be the only one without any bruises...
で お前一人が 無傷っていうんじゃなぁ…
Shut up!
うぜぇ～！ さっきから ピーピー ピーピー うぜぇ!!
This thing's been going "beep beep beep" all friggin' day!
You think I can read all that?!
そんなに文字 読めるか！
What am I going to do about some girl and a bunny?!
何なんだ？ うさぎだ女の子だって オレに言ってどうすんだ!
Shut up!
うぜぇ～！
Huh?
Huh?!
I found the girl. She's okay. It's all settled.
Because...
なぜなら
Because the fortissimo of Ikebukuro has appeared!
Um...
あの…
Hm?
Thank you so much for saving me again.
また助けていただいて ありがとうございました
Who are you?
誰だっけ？
Hey.
おう オレ もう 今日は携帯の電源切ったから
I've turned my phone off for the rest of the day.
See you.
じゃあな
Celty...
セルティさん…
The mission was a success!
All hail the Dollars!
We did it! We did it!
This is what we're made of!
There's nothing to be afraid of if we all help each other out!
Thanks, everyone...
ありがとう みんな
I've found it...
見つかったんだ もう… いちばん大事なことは…
...the thing that's most important to me...
Mikado...?
帝人…
Aww, it's already game-set?
あら～ もうゲームセット!
Shizu-chan sure knows when to get involved.
くぅ～！ シズちゃん いいところで出てくるよねぇ
However, this isn't over yet.
でも まだ終わりじゃない
With this, I'll soon be able to put them
in check and checkmate at the same time.
あと もうちょいで チェックメイトと王手 同時にいけるね これは…
Ah, Celty, it came out! Get that mushroom!
ああ セルティ 出た 出た
そのキノコ 取って
Celty, that's totally impossible.
セルティ それはいくらなんでも無理だよ 無理！
See, that's why I told you to be more careful...
ほら～ だから言ったじゃないか
そこはもっと慎重に…
Eh?! Not that!
うわぁ～ そんな！
Celty...
セルティ…
E-Excuse me.
す… すみませんでした
I didn't want to wake you because you were sleeping so soundly.
I-I'm sorry for causing so much trouble.
ご… ご迷惑を お掛けしてしまって…
It's no trouble at all. Just stick around here for a while.
迷惑なんかじゃないよ
暫くうちに居たらいい
Living by yourself would be dangerous.
一人暮らしは危ないからね
Is that alright?
いいんでしょうか？
If you need anything, I can go get it.
Th-Thank you very much.
あ… ありがとうございます
You're taking some time off from school starting today, right?
今日はもう学校も休むだろ！
I already told Mikado about it, so...
竜ヶ峰君のこと 知ってるんですか？
You know Ryugamine?
Uhh, yeah, somewhat.
うん まあね
Um, I...
あの… 私…
You don't have to worry about anything, Anri.
杏里ちゃんはなんにも心配しなくていいよ
It's okay! I'm on your side, and this shady-looking guy in white is tr—
is, well, a friend.
Hey, what gives?
ねえ な～に？
Why did you start to write "trustworthy," then stop?
なんで 今 信頼できるって 書きかけてやめたの？
Why, huh?
どうして？
ねえ！ セルティ？ ねえ！
Celty?!
What a surprise.
でも びっくりしました
ん？ な～に？
What is?
It's just that I didn't know she lived with a guy.
いえ セルティさん 男の人と暮らしていたんだなぁって
The shogun hasn't shown up since.
将軍 あれから来ませんね
Whatever, it doesn't matter. We know what we have to do.
別にいいんじゃねぇの？ やることは決まってんだからよ
Everyone here knows what we have to do, right?!
ここにいる連中はみんなオレらが何をすべきか 分かってるよなぁ？
We're going to completely crush the Dollars!
これからは 徹底的にダラーズをつぶすぞ！
I'm calling the police!
警察 呼んでくる！
Where are you right now?
あなたは今どこにいますか？
Those yellow guys are at it again.
They're all fired up.
My friend said someone got totally messed up.
We can't afford to lose. Let's pool our resources like we did before.
What are you thinking about right now?
あなたは今何を思っていますか？
The Dollars shall disappear.
What? What does that mean?
What? Isn't that our founder?
Our leader's running away?
Does that mean...we're going to disband?
Huh...
へえ～ ２１時３４分
Nine thirty-four PM: the Dollars of Ikebukuro announce that they'll disband.
池袋ダラーズ 解散宣言っと
That's not it! To "disappear" equals being
"clearly colorless"—the reason why we're the Dollars!
Our leader's so irresponsible.
No he's not! Believe in him!
Say something!
Explain yourself!
The Dollars shall disappear.
You're the worst.
Huh? We can't access it anymore.
あれ？ もうアクセスできないよ!
Really?
マジっすか!
We can view the front page, but the message boards have been completely closed off.
トップページは残ってる けど掲示板は全部閉鎖されちゃってるよ～
Hey, what's this mean?
ねえ これって どういうこと？
It means he's being serious.
つまり 本気ってことじゃ…
That's enough.
もういい ほっとけ
Just drop it.
I had a lot of time to myself, and lots and lots of time to think.
一人でいる時間は長くて
私は たくさん たくさん考えました
Their faces kept appearing in my thoughts.
そうしていると 二人の顔が浮かんできて…
Their smiling faces would appear, and just stay there.
二人の笑顔が浮かんできて 消えません
Um...
あの… お話してもいいですか？
Is it alright...if I have a talk with you?
Of course. I wanted to talk with you, too, Anri.
もちろん 私も杏里ちゃんと話がしたかったから
I feel like I can tell you everything, since you know about me...
私のことを知っているセルティさんなら
全部話せる気がして
I see.
I understand.
So, those two guys you're always with don't know about your true identity.
Kida and Ryugamine are always helping me out.
いつも助けてもらってばかりいました
紀田君にも 竜ヶ峰君にも
And yet, I...
なのに 私は…
First, we have to stop this conflict.
まずはこの抗争を止めないとね
Alright.
はい
I guess the only thing you can do is discuss it with Mikado.
Um...how well do you know him...?
あの… 竜ヶ峰君とは？
Anri, how much do you know about Mikado?
Eh?
So you don't know...
やっぱり知らないか
He's in the same boat as you.
杏里ちゃんと同じだよ
He's hiding something significant from you because you're a close friend and you're important to him.
近くて大事に思ってるからこそ 肝心なことを隠してるのかもね
Anyway, you should ask him yourself.
とにかく 本人から聞いた方がいい
I'll bring him here.
連れてくるよ
Don't get any weird ideas while I'm out.
連れてくるまで いろいろ変なこと吹き込むなよ
Don't bombard her with questions or
perform any crazy experiments on her.
あと 質問攻めにしたり 変な実験しようとするな
I know. Trust me.
分かってるよ 信用して
Okay, I will.
よし 信用した
I won't be long, Anri.
杏里ちゃん 少し待ってて
Celty...
セルティさん
I...don't want to keep running away.
私 もう逃げたくないんです
Let's get out of here!
行くぞ… 行くぞ～！
If you're going to hate someone, hate the guy who ordered us to do this—Kida Masaomi!
恨むんなら命令した紀田正臣を恨むこったな！
制作：lastzzz akira 安静の云
Why couldn't I move that one time?
なぜあのとき 動けなかったんだろう？
What was I hesitating for?
何を迷ってたんだろう？ 何を怖がってたんだろう？
What was I afraid of?
漫游字幕组
http://popgo.net/bbs
Saki, I won't be afraid anymore.
沙樹 オレはもう怖くない
I won't run away anymore.
どこへも逃げやしない
Next Time: All Mixed Up.